slybroadcast.com 2016-03-16

# slybroadcast

**slybroadcast**  is a service of  **MobileSphere.**   **MobileSphere, Inc.**  ( **"MobileSphere"** ) is committed to protecting the privacy of our visitor's personally identifiable information. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is used at our site.

  * MobileSphere collects key information that is necessary to identify you as a unique user, to establish your account, and to allow us to provide our service to you. MobileSphere **does not**  sell or otherwise market information about you!  
MobileSphere does leverage third party services in some areas as part of our service offering. We will not provide the names, email addresses, or phone numbers to any other third party except our service providers who need to use it in connection with providing the specific MobileSphere service.  
MobileSphere collects and processes, or has third party service providers who collect and process on MobileSphere's behalf, information about demographics and usage of the services that help guide and carry out MobileSphere marketing activities. Information usage in this category is general and in no way can be used to identify specific users, phone numbers, or email addresses.

  * MobileSphere respects the privacy of personal e-mail accounts and stores your e-mail addresses as secure information. Your details will not be passed to third parties for their marketing purposes outside of this MobileSphere Service without your explicit permission. MobileSphere may use e-mail to send you messages about faults and service issues. MobileSphere may also use e-mail to keep you up to date with news about the service. If you do not want to be kept informed via e-mail, please [contact us](https://www.mobile-sphere.com/vmb2/contact.php).

  * MobileSphere respects the privacy of personal mobile numbers. Your mobile telephone number is stored as secure information. Your details will not be passed to third parties for their marketing purposes outside of this MobileSphere Service without your explicit permission. MobileSphere may use your telephone number to send you an SMS with the slybroadcast service phone number when you initially use the service and to periodically contact you as a courtesy to ensure your experience is as good as it can be. MobileSphere may also use SMS to keep you up to date with news about the service. If you do not want to be kept informed via SMS, please [contact us](https://www.mobile-sphere.com/vmb2/contact.php).

  * To enhance your experience with our site, we use "cookies." Cookies are used by your computer's browser to store your preferences. We use both session and persistent cookies. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites.

  * MobileSphere collects feedback from visitors to our site. In connection with such feedback, MobileSphere collect names and email addresses. MobileSphere may use the email addresses to contact you regarding your feedback. MobileSphere will not provide the names, email addresses or feedback to any other party except our service providers who may use it in connection with providing the services on our site.  
Any and all information which is voluntarily submitted in feedback forms on the Website is used for the purposes of reviewing this feedback and improving the MobileSphere service and website.  MobileSphere reserves the right to utilize anonymous information for marketing purposes, for instance by displaying selected comments on the Website or in other communications. Further, MobileSphere may from time to time ask you to provide information on your experiences which will be used to measure and improve quality. You are at no time in any obligation to provide any of such data.

  * If a user decides to use our referral tools to inform a friend about our website, service, or special promotion, MobileSphere requests you provide the friend's phone number or e-mail address to send out this specific information. MobileSphere does not record or reuse this information to market to the friend/recipient. Attachments are strictly forbidden and you expressly agree not to add any attachment to any correspondence send via this MobileSphere website. You also agree that you will not use these tools for any other purpose but to share this MobileSphere service with others.

  * MobileSphere may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, for example, in response to a court order, subpoena or a law enforcement agency's request.

  * MobileSphere has put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.  
All information submitted is protected by our secure server, which automatically encrypts your personally identifiable information so that it cannot be read while traveling over the Internet.

  * MobileSphere reserves the right to modify the provisions of this Privacy Statement if deemed necessary. You agree that your continued use of the MobileSphere service shall constitute your acceptance of the Privacy Statement.

  * If you have any questions regarding this statement, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please [contact us](https://www.mobile-sphere.com/vmb2/contact.php).
